harrisbank.com 2002-12-10

# Privacy Summary

Privacy 

At Harris, we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of our customers and  
those who visit our web site. Our Privacy Policy Summary outlines our guidelines for maintaining appropriate and discrete use of information about you. To view our complete Privacy Policy, Click Here. If you use the Harris Total Look service, please Click Here.

The Harris Web site safeguards customer information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard non-public personal information about you. If you'd like to know more about how Harris protects information about you, click on legal for details about our web site security. 

We use your contact information (mailing address, e-mail address and phone numbers) you provide to us to inform you about important information relating to your account, including important administrative information. You have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-administrative information such as information about new products, services or offerings that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive this information by mail, e-mail or telephone in the future, you can tell us not to contact you by contacting us at 1-888-340-2265 or writing to us at Harris Privacy Office, 111 West Monroe, 111/21W, Chicago, Illinois, 60610. Please note that it may take several weeks to fully process your request. Thereafter, the only information we will provide you regarding our services will be through regular communications with you. 

**Please Note:** You can visit our site without providing us with any personal information about yourself to find out about our history, our products and services, and career opportunities we have available.

**What information do we collect about you?**

Harris collects the following types of non-public personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information you provide to us when you fill out an application, complete a form, or make a request for services. This includes your name, address, Social Security Number, assets and income.
  * Information from your transactions with us, such as your account balance, account usage, and loan history.
  * Information obtained from others, such as credit reporting agencies.

This information allows us to:

  * Respond more accurately and efficiently to your requests.
  * Identify opportunities to give you more convenience and control by developing  
new services that may benefit you  

  * Secure your accounts and help protect you, and Harris, from fraud.

**How do we know the information we maintain about you is accurate?**

Harris has established procedures so that our information about you is accurate, current and complete. If you ever discover inaccuracies in our data, or if your personal information changes, we urge you to notify us immediately by calling us at 1-888-340-2265, so that we can make the necessary changes. 

**How do we keep information about you safe?**

We limit access to the information we have about you to those employees who need to know to provide you with a full range of services to help you meet your financial needs. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal laws and regulations to guard your information. 

**When do we share information about you?**

We may share within the Harris family of companies the information we collect about you. However, you as an individual, have a right to instruct us not to share among our banks and affiliated financial service companies certain information (other than information about our  
transactions or experiences with you) from your account applications or information we receive from third parties. Please see our Privacy Policy (Click Here) for more information. 

In addition, we may share information about you with companies outside Harris to complete a transaction you have requested, to help service your account, to provide us operational support, and with other financial institutions with which we have a joint marketing agreement. These companies are not permitted to use your information for anything beyond the intended service and agree to strict standards regarding security and confidentiality. 

These companies may include:   

  * Non-financial companies that perform services for us such as printing your check orders, data processing, and companies that perform marketing services on our behalf.  

  * Financial service providers, including other banks, insurance companies or mortgage companies. For example, we have an arrangement with another financial institution to offer you Harris Bank credit cards.   

We may also share information when required by law or authorized by you. Examples include responding to a subpoena, conducting a fraud investigation, or reporting to a credit bureau.

**Cookies**

It's important to us that your experience with a Harris Web site is effective and satisfying. To accomplish this, we use "cookies" as part of our interaction with your browsers. A "cookie" is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our Web Page Server so it can be read back later from that browser. This is useful for having the browser remember specific information, such as pass codes and log in identification. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or collect personally identifiable information to determine who you are, or capture your e-mail address. The use of cookies is an industry standard - you'll find them almost everywhere on the Internet.

One of the most beneficial uses of cookies is site personalization, where you are able to customize the information you see. For example, by using cookies as part of our internet banking, you can personalize your site. Each time you access your internet banking homepage, the browser will remember your preferences until the cookie expires. Harris also uses cookies to identify what sections of our site are visited most often so we can provide more information on the topics and subjects that our customers are interested in. 

You may determine if and how a cookie will be accepted by your system by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, since some of our applications use cookies to manage your session, disabling a cookie may cause some banking functions to not work properly.

**Children's Online Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect, use, or maintain any information through our websites about children who are under the age of 13. If we determine that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with information through one of our websites, we will only use this information to notify the parents that this information was received. 

**Harris Total Look**

If you use the Harris Total Look service, please review the following:

Harris is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of the account information that you will aggregate through Harris Total Look. Harris' commitment to privacy is reflected in our Harris Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference and made a part of our Harris Total Look Terms and Conditions. Our additional commitments for the Harris Total Look service are that we will treat your account information as follows: 

Harris will not share account information with non-affiliated third parties without your authorization, except to furnish you the Harris Total Look service or as required or permitted by law. We may share account information with Harris affiliates unless you instruct us not to share certain information. Refer to the Harris Privacy Policy for more information, including how you can limit the sharing of certain information with our Harris affiliates. 

Harris will use the account information to furnish and support the Harris Total Look service, and may use such data to allow Harris to offer you relevant products and services, relationship management services, or other financial planning tools. 

Harris may use aggregated, non-personal statistical data derived from your use of the Harris Total Look service for analysis purposes in order to improve Harris' services or products. Yodlee, the provider of this service, may only use your account information and Harris account information to furnish and support the Harris Total Look service. 

Yodlee may use aggregated, non-personal statistical data derived from the use of this service for analysis purposes and may share such information with third parties. 

This privacy policy does not apply to other third party sites you aggregate through Harris Total Look. You should read the privacy policies of all the companies from which you will instruct us to aggregate information. In the event of a change to the Harris Privacy Policy, we will notify you.  

**Additional Information**

To provide you with the best online services, we may direct you to other sites on the Web to  
provide additional information or services that may be of interest to you. Whenever you leave a  
Harris web site, we encourage you to view the privacy policy of the new site. 

**Your best defense with protecting your information on any online service is to make sure you sign-off and close the browser once you have completed transacting business.**
